Guide to the Matthew F. McHugh papers, 1974-1992.
McHugh, Matthew F papers
- District Issues 097, 1980 - 1983 (Box 259)
  Ulster County - Small Business Administration - Amendola, Ulster County - Kingston - Benedictine Hospital, Ulster County - Kingston - Urban Development Action Grant, Ulster County - Kingston - Sewer Break, Ulster County - Medicare Prospective Payment, Ulster County - Kingston - Gateway Industries, Ulster County - Lerchenmueller Case, Ulster County - Town of Llloyd - Conrail, Ulster County - Marbletown, Ulster County - New Paltz - Village, Ulster County - New Paltz - Water Plant, Ulster County - New Paltz - SUNY Migrant Education, Ulster County - New Paltz - SUNY, Ulster County - New Paltz - SUNY Engineering, Ulster County - New Paltz - Gateway Manor, Ulster County - Lake Minnewaska Marriott, Ulster County - Olive, Ulster County - Prattsville, Ulster County - Prattsville 1983, Ulster County - Rochester, Ulster County - Women’s Studio Workshop (2 files), Ulster County - Rosendale -, Ulster County - Rosendale - Five Company Rehabilitation, Ulster County - Rosendale - Proposed Assisted Housing, Ulster County - Rosendale - Town, Ulster County - Rosendale - Village, Ulster County - Saugerties, Ulster County - Saugerties Lighthouse, Ulster County - Shawangunk, Ulster County - Shandaken, Ulster County - Shokan, Ulster County - Stone Ridge, Ulster County - Stone Ridge - Ulster County Community College, Ulster County - Ulster, Ulster County - Uranium Mining, Ulster County - Walkill River, Ulster County - Wawarsing - BioEnergy Systems, Ulster County - Wawarsing, Ulster County - West Hurley - Zena Well Contamination, Ulster County - West Hurley - Route 375, Ulster County - Woodstock, Ulster County - Woodstock Sewer Project 1981, Multi-County 1983 (2" file), Indian Point Nuclear Regulatory Meetings, Out of District, Multi-County - Adverse Effect Wage Rate, Multi-County - Appalachian Regional Commission, Multi-County - Binghamton Wastewater Management, Multi-County - Catskill - Cole House, Multi-County - Commuter Airlines, Multi-County - Delaware River, Multi-County - Delaware River Basin Commission, Multi-County - Hudson Valley Health Systems Agency.
- District Issues 097, 1980 - 1983 (Box 296)
  Sullivan County - Jeffersonville, Sullivan County - Napanoch Sewer Project - Kerhonkson, Sullivan County - Liberty, Sullivan County - Liberty Sewer Project, Sullivan County - Liberty Sewer Plant (2 files), Sullivan County - Liberty Flooding Problems, Sullivan County - Livingston Manor, Sullivan County - Mongaup Valley, Sullivan County - Monticello, Sullivan County - Monticello - Post Office, Sullivan County - Monticello - 1980, Sullivan County - Monticello - 1981, Sullivan County - Monticello - Telephone Office Closing, Sullivan County - Monticello - Sturgis Apartments, Sullivan County - Narrowsburg Landfill, Sullivan County - Neversink, Sullivan County - Neversink Gorge Park, Sullivan County - Rockland, Sullivan County - Roscoe, Sullivan County - Thompson, Sullivan County - Tusten, Sullivan County - Woodbridge, Sullivan County - Wurtsboro, Sullivan County - Wurtsboro Imminent Threat (HUD), Sullivan County - Out of District, Sullivan County - Out of District Roebling Bridge, Tioga County - Miscellaneous - 1982, Tioga County - Miscellaneous - 1981, Tioga County - Miscellaneous - 1980, Tioga County - Miscellaneous - 1979, Tioga County - Miscellaneous - 1977-1978, Tioga County - Tioga Opportunities Program, Tioga County - Apalachin, Tioga County - BRINK, Carl Visit, Tioga County - Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster, Tioga County - Soil & Water District, Tioga County - Berkshire, Tioga County - Candor, Tioga County - Candor - Specialty Packaging, Tioga County - Newark Valley, Tioga County - Nichols, Tioga County - Owego - 1979, Tioga County - Owego - 1980, Tioga County - Owego, Tioga County - Owego - Tioga Casting, Tioga County - Shangri La Speedway, Tioga County - Owego Flood Insurance Study, Tioga County - Richford, Tioga County - Spencer, Tioga County - Waverly - Urban Development Action Grant, Tioga County - Raymond-Hadley Corporation, Tioga County - Tioga (town), Tioga County - Waverly Sewer Project, Tioga County - Waverly - Dry Brook Creek, Tioga County - Waverly (3 files), Tioga County - Ingersoll Rand Retraining Program, Tioga County - River Basin Study Flood Information.
- District Issues 098, circa 1984 (Box 258)
  Ulster/Sullivan counties: Flooding 1984, Multi-County: Gasoline Allocation Regulations, Multi-County: NYS Department of Environmental Conservation, Multi-County: Economic Development, Multi-County: Hudson Valley Regional Council, Multi-County: Emergency Medical Services, Multi-County: Gypsy Moths (2 files), Multi-County: Hudson River Valley Center, Multi-County: Minority Business Opportunity Commission, Multi-County: Miscellaneous, Multi-County: Mobile Radio Distribution, Multi-County: Propane Gas Regulations, Multi-County: Mass Transit, Multi-County: Military Contractors / Pay, Multi-County: NY/PA Health Service Area, Multi-County: New York State Electric and Gas, Multi-County: Nuclear Plants, Multi-County: Pumped Storage, Multi-County: Delaware Releases, Multi-County: Section 18 Rural Transportation, Multi-County: Small Business, Multi-County: Southern Tier Planning & Development Board, Multi-County: Southern Tier Eastern Regional Planning & Development Board, Multi-County: South Central NY Resource Conservation & Development, Multi-County: Railroads: Poughkeepsie Bridge, Multi-County: Community Development Corporation Foster Grandparent Program, Multi-County: Susquehanna River Study, Multi-County: NYS DEC Grant Applications, Multi-County: Susquehanna River Basin Commission, Multi-County: Westway, Multi-County: Casinos, Multi-County: Delaware & Hudson, Multi-County: Sullivanville Dam, Multi-County: Trip to District, Multi-County: Civil Defense, Multi-County: Railroads.
- District Issues 099, 1983, 1984, 1985, 1986 (Box 81)
  Ulster County - Eden Institute (Polish/Jewish), Ulster County - Ellenville 1981-1982, Ulster County - Ellenville 1983-1984-1985, Ulster County - Trudy’s Discovery House, Ulster County - CARNES Sheldon, Ulster County - Senior Housing, Ulster County - Gardiner Sewer Project, Ulster County - Hurley Stone Houses, Ulster County - Human concerns Committee, Ulster County - Comprehensive Employment Training Act and, Job Partnership Training Act Dioslocated Worker Application 1984-1985, Ulster County - Kingston Urban Mass Transportation Administration National Micro, Ulster County - Marbletown Dump, Ulster County - Kingston NYS Job Service, Ulster County - Saugerites Sewer, Farmer’s Home Administration (FmHA) - CONN, Mark, FmHA - Besicorp Group 1985, FmHA - WEED, FmHA - DEMBROSKY 1986, FmHA - 1986, FmHA - SPERLING 1986, Federal Emergency Management Administration: McGuire & Mantell, General Services Administration Procurement, General Services Administration 1986 Samaritan, Multi-County - Community Development Corporation Foster Grandparents, D of Housing and Urban Development Small Cities Program FY 1985, D of Housing and Urban Development Small Cities Program Block Grants 1984, Onteora Enterprises, Small Business Administration: AMENDOLA, Jobs Bill Information 1983, Sullivan County - Swan Lake: WEISER, G., Sullivan County - Montgomery: FIELD, Ed, Sullivan County - Liberty: Walnut Mountain Recreation Park, Sullivan County - Grant Awards 1982, Ulster County - Kingston: Urban Mass Transportation Administration Bus Terminal, Multi-County: Route 209 Ban Delaware Water Gap, Sullivan County - Monticello IRS Closing, Sullivan County - Delaware, Sullivan County - Delaware NYS D of Environmental Conservation, Sullivan County - St. Joseph Forestburgh Postal Service, Sullivan County - Nighland National Park Service Roebling Bridge, Sullivan County - Kiamesha Lake Hebrew Day School, Sullivan County - Mamakating, Sullivan County - Monticello, Sullivan County - Monticello: Post Office, Sullivan County - Monticello: Post Office Annex Closure, Sullivan County - Monticello: Sleepy Hollow, Sullivan County - Monticello: New York Telephone, Sullivan County - Thompson, Sullivan County - Tusten, Sullivan County - Tusten: Cortese Landfill, Multi-County - Grant Awards 1982, Multi-County - Grant Awards 1981, Multi-County - Grant Awards 1980, Multi-County - Marcy South Transmission Project 1985, Multi-County - Marcy South Transmission Project 1983-1984.
- District Issues 099, 1984 - 1986 (Box 245)
  Broome - Endicott, Broome - Superfund Endicott-Colesville, Broome - Endicott, IBM, Broome - Endwell, Broome - Fenton, Broome - Harpursville Central Schools, Broome - Johnson City, Broome - Johnson City - CFJohnson Pool, Broome - Johnson City Sewer Discharge, Broome - Charles Wilson Memorial Hospital, Broome - Johnson City Grace Manor, Broome - Johnson City UDAG HUD, Broome - Johnson City Nezelek Inquiries (2 files), Broome - Kirkwood, Broome - Lisle, Broome - Maine, Broome - Port Dickinson, Broome - Sanford, Broome - Twin Tier Home Health, Broome - Triangle, Broome - Union - Community Development, Broome - Union/Endicott Schools, Broome - Union - Savin Corporation, Broome - Union Town, Broome - Vestal - Vestal Well, Broome - Vestal, Broome - Windsor, Broome - Windsor - UCO Electronics, Broome - Whitney Point, Delaware - Miscellaneous 1982, Delaware - Miscellaneous 1981, Delaware - Miscellaneous 1978, Delaware - Miscellaneous 1980, Delaware - Miscellaneous 1979, Delaware - Delaware Valley Hospital, Delaware - Delaware Opportunities, Delaware - Power Authority of the State of New York (PASNY), Delaware - Delaware River Basin, Delaware - Read Memorial Hospital, Delaware - Lordville Bridge, Delaware - Utsayantha Park, Delaware - West Branch Model Implementation, Delaware - Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster.
- District Issues 099, 1985 - 1986 (Box 244)
  Broome - Binghamton - Roberson Memorial, Broome - Binghamton - Neighborhood Council Coalition, Broome - Rockbottom Dam (2 files), Broome - Savin Corporation, Broome - Secretariat for Education & Project Planning, Broome - Singer Flight Simulator, Broome - Southern Tier East Regional Planning Board, Broome - SUNY Binghamton (2 files), Broome - Trash Dump, Broome - Waste Recovery, Broome - NYS Trade Adjustment Assistance Centers, Broome - Western Broome Bridge, Broome - Binghamton - 1982, Broome - Binghamton - 1981, Broome - Binghamton - 1980, Broome - Binghamton - 1979, Broome - Binghamton - 1979, Broome - Binghamton - Apprenticeship & Training (2 files), Broome - Binghamton - Metrocenter, Broome - Binghamton - GAF Layoff 1980 - 1982, Broome - Binghamton - HUD CD, Broome - Binghamton - Supermarket, Broome - Binghamton - First Ward Levee, Broome - Binghamton - Sludge, Broome - Binghamton - HUD CD 1981, Broome - Binghamton - MONDEV, Broome - Binghamton - City 1980, Broome - Binghamton - Binghamton Savings Bank, Broome - Binghamton - Speech, Broome - Binghamton - Wood Court, Broome - Binghamton - Chenango Bridge, Broome - Chenango Forks, Broome - Chenango Schools, Broome - Conklin, Broome - Kirkwood Flood Protection, Broome - Deposit, Broome - Deposit UDAG, Broome - Watershed (3 files), Broome - Historic Preservation, Broome - Valley Offest, Broome - Dickinson.
- District Issues 099, 1985 - 1986 (Box 289)
  Federal Register & Congressional Record, “Projects” (1" file), Project Tracking (2 files), Delaware Pending, Sullivan Pending, Ulster Pending, Multi County, Out of District, Grants, Questions and New, Sullivan County: Foster Grandparent Program, Clippings (2" file), Indian Land Claims, 12" of Conrail Files.
- District Issues 102, 1991 - 1992 (Box 239)
  Food & Drug Administration - Barr Industries, NYSEG Milliken Station, AIDS Conference 10/91, AIDS Conference 10/89, Food & Drug Administration - Mercury in Dental Amalgam, Rest of Box:, Airline Deregulation 1979 - 1983.
- Energy, 1990 - 1991 (Box 173)
  NYSEG Energy & Water High Phase Order Transmission FY 1990, NYSEG Energy & Water High Phase Order Transmission FY 1991.
- Ethics Committee, circa 1992 (Box 276)
  Congressional Perqs, Reforms, House Bank Scandal (10 files), Miscellaneous Articles.
- Foreign Aid, 1979 - 1986 (Box 57)
  also Export-Import Bank (one file).
- Foreign Assistance & Related Agencies, 1978 - 1980, 2000 (Box 48)
  Published Hearing Records, 1978 Parts 1, 2, 3, 4, 1979 Parts 1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 1980 Parts 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 2000 Global Report to the President, Vol 1: Entering the 21st Century, Pt 2: Technical Report.
- Grants, 1975 - 1979 (Box 287)
  Appalachian Regional Commission 1979 meeting.
- Higher Education in District, 1975 - 1979 (Box 83)
  Files on colleges and universities within district.
- Intelligence Committee, 1988 - 1991 (Box 295)
  General, Cambodia, Nicaragua, Intelligence Appropriations FY 1991, Intelligence Authorization Act 1990 (3 files), Search Procedures Acts 1990, CIPA Hhearings, Angola, FBI & CISPEL, Iran/Contra, Intelligence Authorization Act FY 1991, 1988 Intelligence South Africa, 1990 Intelligence FISA, 1989-1990 Miscellaneous Intelligence.
- Legislative Ratings, 1975 - 1982 (Box 277)
  Four large folders of ratings for 094th, 095th, 096th, 097th Congresses., One binder of 95th Congress Legislative Profile for 1977-1978.
- McHugh Profiles & Ratings (Box 282)
  100th Legislative Profile, 1988 Human Rights Profile, Ratings by Labor Organizations 1975-1992, 098th 099th 100th 101st 102nd Ratings.
- Meetings, 1983 - 1987 (Box 128)
  Meetings in District and DC, prep and follow-up files., Very random..
- Miscellaneous, Various (Box 266)
  102nd HR 1633 (1991) Kids Initiative, 101st (1989-1990) House Continuiing Resolution 259 Harvest of Peace, 100th HR 4575 Debt for Development, 099th First Earth Run, 096th, 097th, 098th, 099th Legislative Profiles, Campaign Finance Reform (four large files).
- Outgoing Information, 1974 - 1984 (Box 164)
  Press Clippings (Five Large Binders), Connie Cook 1984 (opponent), Matt McHugh 1974, 1975, 1978, 1984.
- Outgoing Information, 1975 - 1975, 1979 - 1980 (Box 257)
  94th Congress Press, 96th Congress Press, Check Bouncing (Pro & Con), McHugh Speeches (two huge files).
- Outgoing Information, 1975 - 1978 (Box 84)
  News Clippings 1978, Correspondence "How To" Two large notebooks of form letters filed by issue with index of issues. One book c1977. One book c1975 is the "Wang" system including mix-and-match letter openings, letter bodies, and letter closings..
- Outgoing Information, 1975 - 1978 (Box 139)
  Target Mailings.
- Outgoing Information, 1976 - 1992 (Box 163)
  Press Clippings (Five Large Binders), 1976, 1980, 1981-1982, 1992, Ithaca Journal 6 November 1974 (two copies).
- Outgoing Information, 1979 - 1982 (Box 80)
  Press Clippings randomly filed by issue, person, county, press outlet..
- Outgoing Information, 1980 - 1985 (Box 238)
  Press Clippings.
- Outgoing Information, 1982 - 1985 (Box 254)
  Clippings 1982-1985.
- Outgoing Information, 1982 - 1988 (Box 161)
  Press Clippings (Four Large Binders), Two of Issues Boilerplate Paragraphs 1982-1984, Two of Clippings 1988.
- Outgoing Information, 1984, January 1989 - September 1992 (Box 279)
  Press Files.
- Outgoing Information, July - December 1985, 1986, 1987, 1988 (Box 274)
- Outgoing Information, 1985 - 1986 (Box 278)
  Maine Central Railroad Strike 1986, Conrail Annual Report 1985, Norfolk Southern Annual Report 1985, Conrail Divestiture Plan 1986, Conrail in the Southern Tier, Conrail 1985, Conrail 1986, Press - Ulster & Sullivan Counties, Press - Broome County, Press - Tompkins County, Grant Awards - Sullivan county, Grant Awards - Press, Grant Awards - Tompkins County, Grant Awards - Private sector, Grant Awards - Cornell, Grant Awards - Broome-Tioga-Delaware Counties, Grant Awards - Tompkins County, Grant Awards - Tioga County, Grant Awards - Broome County, Grant Awards - Delaware County, Grant Awards - Sullivan County, Grant Awards - New York State, Grant Awards - Cornell, D of Defense Contracts, Washington Reports, Green Thumb, Inc., Subsidized Housing Issues, Economic Development Act 1979 Public Works Legislation, Appalachian Regional Commission: proposed recissions, Economic Development Task Force, Revenue Act of 1978, Amtrak, Conrail, Community Development Legislation 1979, Women’s Conference on Money & Investments, Railroad Deregulation (two files), Solid Waste Disposal, Appalachian Regional Commission Legislative Information, Urban Mass Transportation Administration Information.
- Outgoing Information, 1989 - 1992 (Box 173)
  1" thick folder of mostly 8x10 B&W glossy photographs of MFM with staff, interns, visitors mostly in DC, some in district venues, very few identified, small envelop of negatives, for more photos see also Box 297.
- Outgoing Information, 1970s - 1980s (Box 246)
  Press Clippings, Radio Feeds, Releases, Ethnica Files, Ortega, Background File on Iran-Contra Hearings.
- Outgoing Information 094, 1974 (Box 114)
- Outgoing Information 094, 1976 (Box 46)
  Press Releases.
- Outgoing Information 094, 1975 - 1976 (Box 208)
  Press Clippings Pre-Session 1975 - December 1976.
- Outgoing Information 094, 1975 - 1976 (Box 82)
  Press Releases 1976 May-Oct, Press Releases 1975, Radio & TV Station Files, Print Media Fils, News Digests, Co-Sponsored Bills 1975, Correspondence re Co-Sponsored Bills 1975.
- Outgoing Information 095, 1978 (Box 98)
  Press Clippings, Background Information, Campaign Information.
- Outgoing Information 095, 1976 - 1978 (Box 113)
  Statements, Letters, MFM stands.
- Outgoing Information 095, 1977 - 1978 (Box 112)
- Outgoing Information 095, 1977 - 1978 (Box 253)
  095th Congress Press Releases.
- Outgoing Information 096, 1977 - 1980 (Box 94)
  Press releases, letters, Washington Reports.
- Outgoing Information 096, 1979 - 1980 (Box 152)
- Outgoing Information 096, 1979 - 1980 (Box 156)
  Press Releases, Newsletters.
- Outgoing Information 096, 1979 - 1980 (Box 290)
  Clippings.
- Outgoing Information 097, 1979 - 1982 (Box 97)
  Press clippings in folders by media outlet.
- Outgoing Information 097, 1981 - 1982 (Box 4)
  Press releases, newsletters, speech texts, announcements, information sheets.
- Outgoing Information 097, 1981 - 1982 (Box 168)
  Ways & Means (Obsolete), Boiler Plate Letters.
- Outgoing Information 097, 1981 - 1982 (Box 262)
- Outgoing Information 098, 1983 - 1984 (Box 5)
- Outgoing Information 099, 1978, 1985, 1986 (Box 166)
  Press Clippings (Four Large Binders), Oct 15-Nov 10 1978, Jan-May 1985, Jul-Dec 1985 Jan-Jun 1986.
- Outgoing Information 099, 1985 - 1986 (Box 247)
  Press Releases, Radio Comments, Schedules, Washginton Reports, “Gary’s Stuff”, Miscellaneous, Dear Colleagues, Town Meeting Notices, Post Office Visits, Staff District Meetings with Constituents, Lists.
- Outgoing Information 100, 1986 - 1987 (Box 165)
  Press Clippings (Two Large Binders), Jul-Dec 1986, 1987.
- Outgoing Information 100, 1987 - 1988 (Box 271)
  Press Releases, Radio Comments, Schedules, Washington Reports, "Gary's Stuff", Miscellaneous Mailings, Dear Colleagues, Town Meeting Notices, Post Office Visits, Staff Meetings with Constitutents, Lists, Imputted Paragraphs, Assorted Mailers.
- Outgoing Information 101, 1989 - 1990 (Box 172)
  Reports to District c1990, Schedules 1989, Schedule 1990, “Gary’s Stuff” 1989-1990, Town Meeting Notices, Post Office Visits, Staff Meetings with Constituents, Lists, Paragraph texts and followups.
- Outgoing Information 101, 1989 - 1991 (Box 162)
  Press Clippings (Four Large Binders), 1989, 1990, 1991, 1991.
- Outgoing Information 102, 1988 - 1992 (Box 195)
  1992 Press Clippings (contents of binder w/o binder), Three schedules from 1992, Statistics 1988-1992.
- Outgoing Information 102, 1989 - 1992 (Box 177)
  Radio Comments, Press Releases 1989 - 1990, Standard Texts, Meet My District Representative, Post Office Cards, Other 500+ Mail, Town Meeting Cards, Dear Colleagues, Schedules, Radio Comments, Press Releases 1991 - 1992, Forms, Inserts 1991.
- Outgoing Information 102, circa 1992 (Box 297)
  2" folder of B&W Photos, for more photos see also Box 173.
- Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, 1987 - 1992 (Box 174)
  McHugh Statements 1987-1992, Ireland Trip, Spt 1991 (Binder), HR 1013 Background File 1987, HR 5422 Intelligence Authorization Act FY 1991 (Binder) 1987-1988, Intelligence “48 Hour Bill” 1988-1990, Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, HR 3822 1987 Intelligence Oversight Act (Binder) 100th Congress.
- Presidential Inauguration, 1981 (Box 308)
  Invitations and programs.
- Project Files, 1975 - 1976 (Box 82)
  Newsletter I May 1975, Newsletter II May 1976, “In”, Chesapeake / Erie-Lackawanna, Proxmire, Biography, Sept 1975 Broome/Tioga Floods, Food Stamp Investigation 1976, Direct Mail (samples of others’ and MFM’s), Democratic National Telethon 1975, Revenue Sharing, Postal Box Rental Bill HR 2573, August Recess 1975, Public Disclosure Records 1974 Campaign.
- Public Works Capital Development Program (HR 11, February 1977), 1975 - 1977 (Box 96)
  Correspondence, Notes, Releases, Meetings.
- Record Votes, 1975 - 1976, 1985 - 1991 (Box 285)
  Nine Bound legal sized books, 094th 1st/2nd sessions, 099th 1st/2nd sessions, 100th 1st/2nd sessions, 101st 1st/2nd sessions, 102nd 1st/2nd sessions.
- Record Votes, 1979 - 1984 (Box 286)
  Eight Bound legal sized books, 095th 1st/2nd sessions, 096th 1st/2nd sessions, 097th 1st/2nd sessions, 098th 1st/2nd sessions.
- Redacted Files, Various (Box 194)
  34 files, names redacted.
- Welfare Reform, 1977 (Box 221)